liveoutthere.com 2014-03-26

# Privacy Policy

LiveOutThere.com is committed to protect your privacy. LiveOutThere.com is informing you of its security measures, its policy on the nature of customer information collected when you order products via the Site, the reasons for which this information is collected, and the use that is made of this information.

### Security

LiveOutThere.com has implemented state-of-the-art security measures in order to protect you against loss or unauthorized use of customer information that is in LiveOutThere.com's possession, notably information concerning your credit card. LiveOutThere.com's servers use the latest information-transmission technology (Secure Socket Layers, or SSL), which render its transmission highly secure. In addition, LiveOutThere.com's servers are protected by firewall technology. LiveOutThere.com ensures its hardware is always state-of-the-art in order to allow you to perform secure transactions on the Site at any time. However, no security mechanism is perfect and you must be aware that you are always at some level of risk that personal information transmitted to LiveOutThere.com may be disclosed without any fault on the part of LiveOutThere.com and without your consent. LiveOutThere.com declines all responsibility regarding forwarded confidential information, except in case of negligence on the part of LiveOutThere.com. Note that, for your security, no information on credit cards is kept on the servers LiveOutThere.com uses.

### What personal information does LiveOutThere.com collect?

LiveOutThere.com requires that you transmit your name, address, e-mail address and other information with your consent while purchasing a product or when entering a contest. To the extent possible, LiveOutThere.com will provide you with the means to verify that the confidential information transmitted are accurate and up-to-date. What use does LiveOutThere.com make of the information collected? Customer information allows LiveOutThere.com to open an account in your name, to process your order, to contact you in the event that you win a prize in a contest, to customize your shopping experience, if you so authorize us, to send you a customized Newsletter. LiveOutThere.com would like to inform you that its advertisers and/or partners do not, at any time, have access to confidential customer information. In addition, LiveOutThere.com does not sell its lists of users. You always have the option to request from LiveOutThere.com that you no longer want to receive the Newsletter by emailing info@LiveOutThere.com and request your email address to be removed from the list.

### Cookies

«Cookies» are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are harmless in that they cannot extract information from your hard disk, over which you have full control. LiveOutThere.com uses cookies mainly in order to determine traffic on the site, to transmit information that is highly usable by its marketing department, and to personalize the future use you make of the site. This technology does not systematically place personal information about you at LiveOutThere.com's disposal. It is always possible to no longer be subject to cookies by modifying your computer's configuration.

### Reservations

LiveOutThere.com reserves the right to modify this policy at any time. LiveOutThere.com also reserves the right to transmit personal information about you to the extent LiveOutThere.com must do so under the law or so as to protect the copyright of the site or those of its users, partners, advertisers or suppliers.
